JESSICA ADAMS

contact

404.644.2075

dentonj24@gmail.com

16 Gould St. @

/in/jessicadadams in.

education

B.A. Mass Communication
Winthrop University
Rock Hill, SC

Studied toward M.A. in Film, Video, and Digital Motion Imaging Georgia State University Atlanta, GA

key skills

Salesforce/Pardot/Hubspot



Wordpress/Drupal



Photoshop/Illustrator



Video Editing (Premiere)



Data Analysis



Problem Solving



profile

Expert marketing professional with 20+ years experience in brand promotion, creative production, and lead generation. Recognized for attention to detail and a complete skillset instrumental to all stages of marketing campaigns—from strategy, to asset creation, to analysis.

professional experience

MARKETING DATA SPECIALIST

Worcester Polytechnic Institute / Worcester, MA / 2015 - present

- •Report analytics and insights regarding sales and marketing leads, ad campaigns, content performance, etc.; ad strategy changes, based on data analysis, resulted in 53% increase in advertising leads over 2 years
- *Design graphics and write copy for marketing deliverables
- *Develop audience personas for advertising targeting and content creation
- *Develop strategy for email drip campaigns and construct campaign drip logic

CONTENT MANAGER

smith&jones idea agency / Sturbridge, MA / 2014 - 2015

- *Specialized in SEO and SEM, writing, placing, and managing digital ads on Google and social networks; increased year-over-year organic website traffic 45.01%
- *Managed online social presence and devised best practices for the agency and clients; increased year-over-year Facebook Page visits 9600% and increased Facebook fan engagement 187.50% over a span of 10 months
- *Designed, wrote, and published e-newsletters; wrote, edited, and published blogs and press releases via WordPress, in addition to other copywriting duties

INTERNET MARKETING SPECIALIST

Vision Advertising / Worcester, MA / 2012 - 2014

- *Created and managed online presence (social media, blogs, press releases, etc.) for a wide variety of clients, including high-end spas, restaurants, and a zoo
- ·Shot, scripted, voiced, and edited promotional videos for clients

COACH (TEAM SUPERVISOR)

T-Mobile Customer Service and Sales Call Center / Augusta, GA / 2010 - 2012

Managed a team of 16 representatives to meet metrics and goals set by the company;
 completed sales certification and coached customer service and sales

OTHER RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

FESTIVAL DIRECTOR / Atlanta Film Festival / Atlanta GA

ON-AIR PERSONALITY / WMKJ / Newnan GA